http://www.slimeathlete.com/show.php?page=privacy

NEWS
[Jun. 04] A Gaming Revolution...Is Coming!
[May. 29] Spread the Word Over AIM
[Mar. 02] Privacy Policy Revised
We're open!
Friday, December 11, 2020
Tell a Friend!
Send IMs about SlimeAthlete!
AIM Screennames
Or, you can send SlimeCards via e-mail.
Policy Coverage
This privacy statement governs the collection, use, and dissemination of personal data from visitors to the SlimeAthlete web site.
All aspects of the presence are subject to these provisions with the exception of SlimeAthlete affiliate advertisements and any other references beyond the slimeathlete.com domain which may not necessarily indicate endorsement, in part or whole, by SlimeAthlete of the referred sites’ practices.
Questions or comments regarding privacy conduct by SlimeAthlete beyond the considerations stipulated below should be directed via e-mail (info@slimeathlete.com) or mail (3 Teal Lane, Essex, Connecticut 06426-1046).
Throughout this policy, the terms “we” and “us” refer to SlimeAthlete, a division of PolariStar LLC.
Information Collection
SlimeAthlete may ask for personal information such as a visitor’s name, address, age, etc. in conjunction with a transaction on our web site either as requested by the visitor (e.g., account signup) or as requested by SlimeAthlete (e.g., a survey).
Under any circumstance the visitor --- at his or her sole discretion --- has the opportunity to choose not to provide the information for which they are prompted.
By declining such a request, a visitor understands that his or her access to subscription-based services may be compromised.
Any submission of personal information to SlimeAthlete is usually held for a period of a few months, but may be maintained longer pending notification of such housing at the point of data entry.
Once a visitor has submitted personal information, he or she may not request that it be removed from SlimeAthlete’s systems except when a written petition is made to demonstrate how such collection was impermissible in accordance with Connecticut State law, Federal law, or this privacy policy.
Disclosure of User Data to Third Parties
Personal information collected by SlimeAthlete is not rented, sold, or in any other manner distributed beyond the realms of the SlimeAthlete staff and its parent company, PolariStar LLC, except in the following scenarios:
We provide information to a third party group operating under a confidentiality agreement with us to assist in our efforts to serve content and marketing materials; such an establishment would be forbidden to further distribute information
We receive a court order, subpoena, or other request from a legal body to release information or if we are in a position to defend against legal claims; we may also proactively release user information if we suspect illegal activity, fraud, or an intent to commit harm originating from one or more user(s) of our web site
We transfer ownership of SlimeAthlete and/or PolariStar LLC to another firm or forge a merger with another company; in this case, we will make prominent notification of such, including statement about how the current privacy policy may be altered
Additionally, affiliate programs posted on our site may be targeted by geographic location, interests, or other criteria.
These third-party organizations assume that users who interact with such advertisement materials fit the aforementioned specification; however, SlimeAthlete will under no circumstance provide validation of such an assumption or any other indication --- suspected or confirmed --- about a user’s background beyond that we targeted a given ad program with the understanding that it was relevant to our visitor.
Third Party Advertising
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php>.
Children Under 13
In compliance with COPPA, SlimeAthlete will not ask children under thirteen (13) years of age to submit personal or identifying information without parental consent, nor will we proactively contact members of our visitor base under 13 with any promotional offers of our affiliates.
Additionally, we strongly encourage parental supervision and/or permission whenever a child under 13 makes any form of transaction with us.
Cookies
As part of our effort to improve service at SlimeAthlete, we periodically post and retrieve small amounts of cookie data (a few bytes in size) on our visitors’ computers.
This information is accessed solely to examine service popularity and visitor access patterns within SlimeAthlete.com; these cookies are neither set nor accessed outside the SlimeAthlete.com Internet identity by SlimeAthlete or its affiliates.
However, please note that our affiliates (who we allow to place ads on certain parts of our web site) may set and access unrelated during a user’s visit with us.
These cookies are subject to the affiliates’ respective privacy policies which are therefore not subject to the terms outlined herein.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
Confidentiality
SlimeAthlete employs security mechanisms wherever possible to protect the confidentiality of information you submit to us.
Although portions of this data may be available to our employees, it is only open in such a manner as deemed reasonably necessary for our staff to complete its assigned tasks.
Policy Changes
This policy is subject to change when SlimeAthlete, at its sole discretion, considers a change in its practices to merit alteration of the terms set forth herein.
Whenever such changes are made, SlimeAthlete will do its best to post notice of such in a prominent location on its website (usually in the “News” section of the presence).
© 2020 SlimeAthlete.com / PolariStar LLC. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy | Disclaimer | Company | Contact
Plot IP - Your Source for Web, Domain Name, and IP Address Information
